Something I think a lot of people are missing is that the attempt to control how people are able to respond to something, particularly solely with words, is not something that stops.
It doesn't find a limit and say, OK, we're going to stop now.
So the people who are engaging in perpetuating that thought control seem to think that they are absolved of it ever being turned on them, not realizing that in engaging in that, in perpetuating the effort of the United States government to actively invade people's free speech, they are invading their own free speech.
And they may think, well, yeah, but I agree with them, so I'm not going to ever be in danger.
And that's simply just untrue because dominance is not about simply just agreeing.
Like on the Night of the Long Knives, the leader of the Third Reich took out people who avidly agreed with him because he felt that they were getting more power than him.
You see, the issue is not whether or not you are in alignment with these people or whether you are in agreeance with their stance.
The issue is power and any threat to that is a threat to you.
So I just wanted to illuminate that because what's happening now is this very myopic argument around how one should respond to something.
And that is what is designed.
They want us distracted with that while they do a bunch of other things that are deeply harmful to everybody, regardless of how you responded to this person.
And the real goal is to simply just keep folks dominated.
That's the actual goal.
And if you are engaging in that, you too have been dominated.
And you're being dominated by a government that doesn't even care about you.